# Saleh Salehizadeh

Web Developer, Data Analyst

# +98 (919) 724 6908 ⊠ animatorsaleh@gmail.com in saleh-salehizadeh SirSalh SirSaleh sirsaleh on Stack Overflow

Why do we fall bruce? So we can learn to pick ourselves up  $\sim ThomasWayne, BatmanBegins$ 

#### summary

whoami I am Saleh. A full-stack web developer and statistics enthusiast. since childhood, I've been programming for fun, and now I'm developing web for almost 6 years. my main fields of working were entertainment and transportation industries, using Django, PHP, R, MySQL, PostgreSQL and etc. Creating Interesting and useful systems is what connects all my interests and experiences.

## Education

2015-2018 M.Sc., Amirkabir University of Technology, Tehran, Mathematical Statistics.

2010–2014 B.Sc., Allameh Tababaei University, Tehran, Applied Statistics.

Master thesis

title Simultaneous Tests For High Dimensional Datasets

supervisors Dr. Omid Naghshineh, Dr. Adel Mohammadpour (adel@aut.ac.ir), Dr. Mina Aminghafari

Rapporteur Dr. E. Khorram and Dr. Ahmad Parsian

description Nowadays emergence of new technologies like Mircroarray has been leaded to creating large scale datasets. Datasets which number of variables are a hundred times as their sample sizes. As the usual methods like  $T^2$ -Hotelling for simultaneous comparison of means in such datasets, there exists a need for new methods. In first, this thesis, different methods for comparison of mean vector will review. Then a new applicable method in Behrens-Fisher setting, (assumption of non-equal variance in testing means of two populations) and invariant under shift and scalar transformations introduced. This method implemented using C++ in  $\mathbf{R}$  and the performance of the implementation has been investigated.

BSc. Project

title Investigation on Mobile-Bank Service Based on SERVQUAL Model

## Experience

Sep 2015- **Website Management and WordPress Developer**, Allmaeh Tabatabaei University, Tehran.

Nov 2016 Working on atue.ir website and shop and bank gateway. used Technologies: Wordpress, MySQL, Woocommerce

WordPress Developer, ATNA (Allameh Tabatabei News Agancy), Tehran.

Project Fix some major bugs in website, including problems in front-end and implementation of home page slider

May 2018- Full-stack django Developer, Boundar Souban Samaneh, Tehran.

April 2020 Irasography is a website for photographers and photography enthusiast people. This website provides services for photographers to show their art, and for companies to order their photography needs. irasography.com.

> I was responsible for implementing API endpoints and front-end UI. Used technologies were django, postgresql, bootstrap, nginx, etc.

September Part-time full-stack developer, Rest API, and management dashboard, Parastoo Co., 2019- present Tehran.

Abrbar is a transportation project in order to manage shipment of cargoes. Used by truck drivers and cargo companies. My task is Implementing restful API which currently uses in both drivers and customers android app and abrbar dashboard

used technologies: Django, postgresql, Nginx, reactjs, PWA, jquery, etc.

September Part-time Back-end developer, DNBuy Co., Tehran.

2020- present *Dnbuy is a domain and hosting provider website*. My task is to participating to new dnbuy service implementation.

used technologies: Django, Nginx, MySQL, jquery, etc.

# Languages

English Advanced

Arabic Beginner

Japaness Beginner

# Computer and programming skills

Linux 6 Years User of Linux OS 🔬, when the linux of Linu

Web Familiar to django framework (for instance django dongy app available in github and con-Development tributing in django allauth, developing djang-simple-chart, irsasography photographers platform, and abrbar project). Prgramming in PHP, MySQL. and wordpress development. currently sometimes learning GO language. Familiar to HTML, CSS3. Familiar to Bootstrap CSS framwork.

Serverside familiar to Deploying django app using nginx and uwsgi

Deployment

Statistical R, more than 4 years experience on R programming for statistical purposes. Familiar with R base Programming functions and packages like ggplot2 and FactoMineR, Familiar to SPSS, SAS, and Tableau

VCS Familiar to git, and gitflow

### Interests

Routine Interested in learning New topics in technologies and human languages. Reading 🖹 stackoverflow and other Stackexchange sites and try to answer the questions.

job interests Web Development, Statistical Research

#### Courses

 AUT and Paris 5 university courses on applied statistics (Clustering, Random Forests and Extreme Value Theory)